



As a **front-end developer** from a healthcare background, I am all about the user experience: I create clean designs with accessible and readable code, and value inclusive and welcoming environments. You can find me following tennis and Toronto's sports teams, as well as brushing up on languages inside and outside of tech.

Toronto, ON | e: sabine.tait@gmail.com

# Education

Immersive Web
Development Bootcamp

Juno College 2021 - 2022

Honours Bachelor's of Science Human Kinetics

University of Guelph 2011 - 2015

## Skills

#### Core

- Bilingual: English/French
- Clear & effective communicator
- Detail oriented
- Enthusiastic collaborator
- Thrives on organization

LIVE | CODE

LIVE | CODE

#### **Technical**

- HTML5 / CSS3
- JavaScript (ES6)
- Sass
- RESTful APIs
- Responsive web design
- React
- Firebase
- Version control, Git & Command line
- Paired/Peer programming
- Accessibility

# **Featured Projects**

### **Arcane Memory Game**

HTML5 | CSS3 | Sass | JavaScript

A fun Vanilla JavaScript memory game. Users draw two cards at a time to find all the characters from Arcane: League of Legends. Matching cards remain face-up, while non-matches flip over

#### Stars Align

React | CSS<sub>3</sub> | API

Horoscope app that allows the user to get their daily horoscope and other compatibilities with data from aztroAPI based on their astrological sign and the current date

## Flip It and Reverse It

LIVE | CODE

React | Sass | API | Firebase

Paired-programming backronym generator app made with data from the DataMuse API. Users enter in a word to generate their own backronym, and save the ones they like!

#### **Bite-Sized Traveling**

LIVE | CODE

React | CSS3 | API | Firebase

Peer-programming travel app created based off a client brief allowing users to create trips and add/remove restaurants to their list based on their search locations. The user is also able to add notes to specific restaurants

# Recent Experience

### Office Manager | First Care Centre

2015 - 2021

- Used refined communication and organization skills to manage 7 practitioners' schedules in order to maximize clinic hours and maintain a personable experience with patients
- Streamlined all patients' paper files to an updated digital web-based patient management system, and implemented electronic billing to over 85% Canadian insurance companies
- Updated social media pages and maintained accurate information on Google and OpenCare with office news, marketing material, and wellness tips to ensure community presence

#### Bilingual Seasonal Receptionist | Unique Gas Products

2012 - 2015

- Handled all consumer and dealer products inquiries (English/French), resolved complaints, facilitated returns, and directed fulfillment issues to the appropriate company personnel
- Supported sales/marketing teams in the organization and distribution of bilingual POP marketing material to North American dealers to successfully launch 17 new products
- Key translator for technical support to facilitate communications with French speaking dealers and consumers